## Ms. Hunter Pesqueira

(520) 555-1234 or hpesqueira@email.arizona.edu

# **Objective**

Four years of college experience obtaining a Bachelor of Science degree in Public Health at the University of Arizona. Three years in customer service and a receptionist position for facility communication. I apply all capable abilities to the jobs I invest myself in to bring my strong work ethic to any task. I am excited to grow my knowledge and work force in medical fields that will lead me to the job of working as a Medical Examiner in the future. Comfortable with applications of MW, ME, SpaBiz, Adobe Photoshop. Past experiences allow me to be comfortable with consumer communication in all situations, remain calm in stressful situations, and have taught me to overpower any opportunity's that I may come across.

#### **Education**

- University of Arizona, Tucson, Senior majoring in Public Health (2017 2021)
- Mt. View High School, Tucson, AZ, graduated May 2017

### **Work Experience**

Receptionist, Bloom Salon and Beauty Bar (March 2019 – June 2019)

Provided exceptional customer service to salon clients and visitors including:

- Maintained a clean, sanitized, and well organized work environment
- Answered phones, booked appointments and maintained client records
- Conducted inventory and replenished stock of supplies
- Processed payment transactions

Sales Associate, Beauty Brands (August 2017 – February 2019)

Beauty product sales and customer service including:

- Assisted customers with questions on products and services
- Notified supervisor of supply needs to ensure necessary items were in stock
- Met and exceeded sales goals
- Developed on-going relationships with customers

Office Assistant, Hunter's Tile Interiors, LLC (Summers 2015 and 2016)

Assisted Bookkeeper in the light duties including:

- Answered phones
- Responsible for billing and filing paperwork (invoices, accounts payable, payroll)
- Delivered employee checks and materials to job sites

#### **Extracurricular Activities: Alpha Chi Omega**

• Platform: Domestic Violence (August 2018 – present)

#### References

• Available upon request